kimi ni kono koe ga
So that my voice
todokimasu youni
is able to reach you,
karamitsuku kaze o surinuke ima negau yo
I hope to survive this entangling wind.
ashita o sekasu kodou ni
I will be completely without direction,
boku wa itsu kara ka tomadoi kakushiteta
in the fast paced world of tomorrow.
samenai yume ni mayotte
When I was lost in my own dreams,
kuri kaesu hibi ni ibasho o sagashiteta
I was looking for a place to belong in this modern age.
kimi ni deai muryoku o shiri
When I met you, I learned what true strength is.
kakae kirenai hikari ni mo fureta
Now that I've touched what could barely be seen,
soko ni nani ga atte imi naku aretatte
Without any other knowledge, without having a solid reason,
kotae awase ja tsumaranai
I've found my answer that a skeptic would just ignore.
kimi ni kono koe ga todokimasu youni
So that my voice is able to reach you,
yaketsuku toki o surinuke ima negau yo
I hope to survive this scorching era.
'I'll be back!'
I've returned! Gaaash.
It's Patie!
Damn! We just fought not too long ago
and you're already here for payback?!
Oh, payback? What do you mean?
I've come to burn your book
for sure this time.
What?!
Now, come forth, the warriors
from a thousand years ago.
Patie's Revenge!!
The Release of the Assassins
Warriors from a thousand years ago?
What does that mean?!
They've been revived.
To eliminate all the remaining demons.
What?!
Like I said.
Your book...
is about to be burned.
Now then, my servants.
Go forth and destroy them!
Garon!
That was close.
What? Why are these strange
enemies so eager for battle?
Gash!
Three enemies at once!
How do we handle this?
They've caught up to us!
Damn! He's casting a spell!
Gash! Kick the demon's right leg!
Now! Hit him as hard as you can!
No, we have to find a
place without any people.
Right!
Monsters!
So dramatic! So dramatic!
The fight's just started
and you're already out of breath.
Patie, if they're from
1,000 years ago, then...
Were they in the previous fight to
decide the ruler of the demons?
You got it.
What else would they be?
Then why are they here?
One thousand years later,
in the human world!
Does it have to do with
their rage and hatred?
That's right.
I'll answer your question.
But, these demons won't
stop fighting for that.
Will you survive long enough
to hear the whole answer?
Garon!
Guransen!
Biraitsu!
Rashirudo!
Good, we deflected them!
Now they'll attack them instead!
Bireiorudo!
Now he deflected them?
All of them at once?!
See? Aren't they strong?
They've got thousand years of malice
pent up inside them from being stone.
There's no way you can beat them.
What? Stone?
Watch out!
That's right.
These demons met something named the
Stone Golem in the battle 1,000 years ago.
He transformed them and their
books into living stone!
The poor dears.
Unable to return to the Demon World,
they were forced to remain as
stone tablets, about this big.
Stone tablets?
Could it be?
The stone tablets Dad and I found?!
Oh, so you know of them.
That makes things easier.
They owe it all to Lord.
She freed them from
their everlasting hell.
Like an angel.
Lord?!
You mean... her?!
And you two have been chosen
to receive their anger...
as sacrifices.
Guranga Cobra!
Bring forth the power!
The strong power of our hearts!
Strong enough to deflect this spell!
Zakeruga!
Good, he's in range!
That's... one down.
Using only the minimum spell
needed to subdue the enemy.
It shows your level of
experience in this battle.
If you don't conserve your spells, you run
out of life energy to continue the fight.
But, when fighting enemies
from 1,000 years ago...
that won't work.
Their bodies are much stronger than ours.
Kiyomaro!
What?
I simply adore those faces!
Those looks of despair!
Can you feel how your chances
of winning have crumbled?
And what's worse is that they still
haven't used their strongest spells.
What?!
Good bye, Gash-chan.
I'll beat you to a pulp
and make you disappear!
Zakeruga!
Damn! That was a direct hit!
He should have fallen!
Ganzu Biraitsu!
Gash, this way!
Right!
Kiyomaro!
Gash. Carry me on your
shoulders and run! Hurry!
Right!
They're getting away.
Go catch them and finish them off!
Good. They've all lined up
together and followed us in here.
Stop, Gash!
This will decide it!
Against these three enemies,
this is our only chance!
Take this and prepare to be defeated!
Baou Zakeruga!
Daibara Biranga!
Gigano Garanzu!
Go!
What?
Two of them at once?
No! The Baou Zakeruga...
We've lost...
Kiyomaro!
Hang on, Kiyomaro!
Is... Is it over?
It looks like even your strongest
spell wasn't good enough.
Shut up!
We're not done yet!
Brave words.
But it took all your strength to hide
your book under your body.
Oh, you're going to keep
fighting without any spells?
What touching courage.
But I won't be lenient!
Let me go!
Patie, I have one question.
What is it?
Why do the thousand-year-old demons
have humans able to use their books?
You stumbled onto an interesting point.
You're right, no human could
live for a thousand years.
Zakeruga!
They used their own comrade as a shield?
How despicable...
Comrade?
Gash-kun. You're risking your life by letting
such a foolish feeling get in your way.
Foolish you say?
Right. They are just underlings.
Without a conscience or feelings,
they are just tools.
That's why we can do this.
No way.
Ladomu!
So that's it.
When they see Baou Zakeruga,
almost anyone would balk.
But their partners, far from being scared,
managed to counterattack.
Just like their demons, they
show no hesitation in battle.
Kiyomaro?
In other words, they don't have a
single thought beyond the battle.
No thought outside the battle?
You mean...
I'm sure of it.
They're being controlled by Lord!
So it really is Lord!
So that's why Lord respects you so much.
But why can they use the books?
Alright, I'll tell you.
In some distant ruins, Lord
found the stone tablets.
She revived the demons and their books.
Then they told Lord the names of their
partners from 1,000 years ago.
Giving the books to her servant Byonko,
she sent him to their homelands
to search for their descendants.
And she gathered everyone
whom the books reacted to.
Of course, the fact they were descendants
wouldn't mean they could use the books.
So she experimented
on them, one by one.
But almost none of them
could even read the books.
Not one of them was able
to actually cast a spell.
So the human's heart and the books
must be perfectly me... me...
Meshing gears?
Right! The gears didn't mesh.
Then how is it that
those gears mesh now?
With Lord's power.
With her ability to control minds,
she forced the humans to match
the difference in the books.
And if their minds match,
now the wa... wa...
Wavelengths?
Right! Now the wavelengths
matched perfectly.
And taking advantage of this, she made
them concentrate only on the battle.
You know, there are humans
who dislike fighting.
And cowardly people, and
tender-hearted people.
Those kinds of people have to be made
into fighting machines to be of use.
That's why we erased everything
except their will to fight.
And now, look!
They're strong enough to easily
bring you to your knees.
Shut up!
Damn it!
Do you... have any idea
what you're doing?!
What's wrong with you?
You can't even move, and you
still want to fight me?
This isn't a game!
Manipulating the hearts of those who don't
want to fight and forcing them to fight?!
I know someone like that!
I won't let him live!
Koruru!
Koruru... I'm Shiori, remember?
Damn it.
Why are you smiling?
That's right.
You're turning back to normal.
You're Koruru.
Damn it!
My sweet Koruru...
Thank you, Gash-kun,
for stopping Koruru.
Huh? Gash?
Why am I here?
Sis Shiori! You're hurt!
This...
Even though I...
I did all this...
My other side got out, right?
And everyone got hurt!
She was crying tears of pain!
And now you're doing things
even worse than her!
So what?
You can't even move to cast your spells!
Don't pretend you can still fight!
This isn't a game!
Controlling people's minds...
Forcing peaceful people to fight...
You cowards!
I can never forgive that!
We can't lose.
We can never let anyone
like that become the ruler!
You're right, Kiyomaro!
We won't lose to them!
I never...
want to see those tears...
ever again!
What? What are you doing?
Thousand-year-old warrior!
Hurry and beat them!
Gash!
Zakeru!
Is that all?
I see, so you're at your limit.
Your last attack didn't
have a bit of power in it.
Damn...
Hmph. Give up.
No matter how hard you cry,
you can't win!
There are close to 40 of the
thousand-year-old demons.
They fight better!
They're bigger!
Two meager bugs talking big
can never match them!
Guransen!
Ganzu Biraitsu!
Garon!
Come on, spells!
We can't lose here!
We can't let them become ruler!
Seushiru!
Tio!
Megumi-san!
What?
Gash! Kiyomaro!
You two aren't alone!
You've got strong allies too, don't you?
Stars atarashii mirai e to...
Stars, to the new tomorrow...
akiramenai hitori janai
don't give up, you are not alone
mou mayowanai yeah...
I have no more doubts, yeah...
me no mae no genjitsu ni
to the truth before my eyes
he kon de shimau koto hoshi no kazu
to the things I give in to, the number of stars
yuugure no aka wo mita
I saw the redness of evening
boku ni hitsuyou na kawaranai yuuki
the unchanging courage that I need
boku wa boku de kimi wa kimi no
me and mine, you and yours
yuzurenai jounetsu
unyielding passion
me wo sorasazu ni tatakai tsuzukeru koto
don't turn your eyes away, continue to fight
We've gotta take the stars
sorezore no nido to nai toki wo kizamou
try to carve the moments that won't come again
shinjitsu wa Rhythm Nation
truth is Rhythm Nation
toki no nagare ni makenaide arukou
don't lose to the flow of time, walk...
You don't have to worry about tomorrow
Let's show them our combination, Gash!
Who is that girl?! Why's she
so friendly to Gash-chan?!
Tio! Megumi-dono!
Fight with us!
All you weaklings will
be crushed together!
This fight isn't about numbers!
Now you'll see our new spell!
Next time on Konjiki no Gash Bell:
The Light of Hope, Saifojio.
Don't worry, Kiyomaro.
Believe in us, your friends!
The Light of Hope, Saifojio