ashita he tsuzuku sakamichi no tochuu de
On the uphill road that leads to tomorrow
surechigau otona tachi wa tsubuyaku no sa
We pass by adults who tell us this
"ai toka yume toka risou mo wakaru kedo
"I can understand ideals such as love and dreams
me no mae no genjitsu wa sonna ni amaku nai" tte
but the real world isn't as easy as you think"
tsumazuki nagara mo korogari nagara mo
Even though we keep tripping and falling
kasabuta darake no jyounetsu wo wasuretaku nai
We have to remember these pains of growing up
otona ni narenai bokura no
For all of us who can't force ourselves to do so yet
tsuyogari wo hitotsu kiite kure
Listen to this one thing I have to say
nige mo kakure mo shinai kara
I won't run or cower away
waraitai yatsu dake warae
So whoever wants to laugh at me, go ahead
semete tayori nai bokura no
Since we can't be relied upon yet
jiyuu no me wo tsumitoranai de
Don't take away our seed of freedom
mizu wo ageru sono yakume wo
The task of nurturing this plant
hataseba iindarou?
That's all we have to do, right?
Finishing blow!
Damn it!
This fight ends here.
I shall look forward
to our next encounter.
But do not forget I could have
burned your book at any time.
Meru Meru Mee!
Umagon Critical Danger?!
It's okay now, Umagon.
Don't be too concerned, Umagon.
Gash lost.
Please leave him be.
That aside, Umagon.
Why do you completely disregard me?
His words are literally "Why do you not even go to
scoop/pump water for me?" (e.g. from a well),
it's a saying that Umagon turns into a pun.
You little horse!
Umagon.
I have a request...
I'd like to borrow your room for a while.
Okay, Umagon?
You mustn't look inside
until I say it's ok.
Kiyomaro is incredible!
I will save you.
I will teach you.
Yes.
I'm going to move towards
being a kind ruler,
a step at a time.
Umagon!
I shall fight by your side.
Baou Meruga!
We did it, we defeated the enemy.
You are so strong!
Zakeru!
No, no, you can't do that.
A horse cannot ride the train.
You can't even buy a ticket,
so don't throw a tantrum.
Ah, I feel refreshed.
Umagon, thank you.
Potato Chips
Cheese
Umagon?
Hey, there's a horse in a place like this.
What book is this?
I've never seen this language.
I can't read it at all.
What is this book?
What weird writing,
is this horse foreign?
No, no!
You should go home.
Umagon-chan knows how
to eat at a table.
You should be proud.
Making sheep noises is no use.
I refuse to share my food
with horses or sheep.
Hey, it's a horse.
Can I feed it?
Yes, of course.
Give it some of this.
Mr. Horse, eat this.
Here, Umagon.
Awful
Hey, it won't eat.
Hmm. It's crying.
Sniff, sniff.
This way!
That Umagon, where on
earth is he headed?
Oh, sorry.
Delivery
What, you're anxious about what kind
of person will be your book keeper?
Don't worry.
I'm sure it will be a good person.
Oh dear.
You're not sure what
kind of person is good?
Let's see...
A good person you would
recognize straight away.
I know!
The nice-looking gardener at
the hay store we always visit.
Probably someone like that.
Hey, Schneider-kun!
This hay is really tasty!
Oh my, this kid.
I wonder where his anxiety went?
Now, Schneider-kun!
Merumeru, let's defeat the enemies!
Ah, I won't ask you anymore,
you coward.
I'll do something about that on my own.
What's with this horse?
This book is...
Wow, isn't it great?
You've finally met your book keeper.
This is great!
By any chance, do you...
understand human speech?
Yes, he does!
Okay, you two are hungry, right?
I'll invite you to my house.
Oh, thank you.
Come on in.
This is my house.
There are lots of interesting things!
My job is to deliver
presents to poor people.
So, this is for...
You are really a good person.
Aww, stop that.
You're embarrassing me.
Say, how would you like
to help me with my job?
What would we need to do?
I'd like you to help
me carry the presents.
Oh? Leave it to us!
That's a great help to me.
It would be best if I could drive a car,
but if I try to get in one,
the horn won't stop.
That's a problem.
So because of that, your help would certainly save me...
I guess.
I understand!
Oh, you will take on this job?
Right! From now on we are partners.
Please do your best.
My name is Dorouma Kotarou.
Please call me Doronma.
I am Gash Bell.
And this is...
Schneider!
Your name is... Umagon.
Yeah, I thought this ever
since I first saw you.
If I were to give this horse a name,
it would definitely be Umagon.
That's it! It's Umagon!
Whoa!! Stop it! Don't bite.
Right! We're off!
This is incredible.
At this rate, my job of delivering
presents will become easy.
Ok, you two can wait here.
I've kept you waiting.
Let's get going.
Okay, let's go home for the night.
This is great, thanks to
you two my job went well.
To have reaped such a yield.
I mean, gathered so many
presents, is a first!
We're going to deliver these
to poor people, right?
Here, presents for all!
Wow!
Doronma-san!
Well, all of this is thanks
to my fabulous partner.
Thank you, Umagon.
Okay! Now let's do some more work!
Yeah!
And we're off!
But we haven't loaded anything.
Let's go!
Okay, here we go!
Here we go again!
We must hurry, Umagon!
Ah, ah, you guys really are great.
Umagon. Gash-gon.
This is it, the scene of the robbery?
Yes, that's right, inspector Shakotan.
Clearly the work of a pro, isn't it?
Hmm... This technique...
It has to be him.
That legendary phantom thief.
This is the work of Doronma!
My technique and your swift feet.
This just might work out.
Okay! We're going to try
a major challenge.
Challenge?
Yes. A big job I have not
been able to do on my own.
Plan
This is a big house.
My precious present is
hidden in this mansion,
and I want to retrieve it.
There are all kinds of traps
in that mansion,
but with that present I could
save a lot of poor people.
You'll help, won't you?
Of course!
Okay, we're sneaking in.
Oh, there are lots of mean-looking dogs.
Watch-dogs? Hmph.
You can't do this job if
you're afraid of dogs.
I see. Okay, let's go, Umagon.
If we take this and feed it to the leader,
any dog would... Uh?
Take this!
Haha! I win!
Such an unnecessary move.
Quickly, inside the mansion!
Okay, from here on, use this scope.
Wow! Pretty!
You can see the red lines, right?
If you touch them, the alarm switch will...
Aww! That's not fair, Umagon.
Run, you two!
Grr... In that case we must
finish the job at once.
It does not matter what you think I am.
The one who has been called
the artist of thievery.
This is a display of phantom
thief Doronma's skill!
I've stepped on the spikes.
It hurts!
Argh, that's enough!
You guys just stay there.
The safe is just in front of me.
You can just be of use when I run away.
So, I'm saying I was just pulling your leg.
Damn it, I need to hurry.
I took far too much time.
Okay, with this, the PIN code to
open the safe will be revealed.
Just one more...
Incorrect PIN code.
As a security measure, the
PIN code will be changed.
Incorrect PIN code.
You idiot!
As a security measure, the
PIN code will be changed.
I told you to stay over there!
Doronma, what are you doing?
You must stop!
Darn, I've wasted even more time.
Ok, I've got the diamond.
We're escaping!
You are completely surrounded!
Surrender peacefully!
We've set off every alarm there is.
I guess it's natural this has happened.
I don't want to be caught.
I finally got the "goronbingu
diamond super-one"!
Huh? The super-one is...?!
All you poor people!
Thank you for waiting!
I'll give you a present now!
Such... Such a needless action...
This is inspector Shakotan.
I have arrested phantom
thief Doronma.
The diamond is safe.
Haha.. You two really were a big help.
Hurry up and get in.
They're going to take
Doronma somewhere!
You...
You're trying to protect me?
Thank you...
But you know, I'm really... a thief.
What? Is that true?
Yeah. Sorry about deceiving you.
You really are a good kid.
From now on, I will try hard to be
a person who deserves your trust.
Then, then what will
happen to Umagon?
The future battles?
Fights?
That's right. You were able to read
Umagon's book, weren't you?
Book?
Oh, right. This book.
Ah, it was this page.
Look. A fly got squashed and died.
Here, you can have it back.
But what country is this book from?
I couldn't read it at all.
Bye now.
Cheer up, Umagon.
I'm sure one day a wonderful
partner will appear for him too.
You'll need to look after this.
Now let's go home, Umagon.
Mother's delicious food is waiting!
Stars atarashii mirai e to...
Stars, to the new tomorrow...
akiramenai hitori janai
don't give up, you are not alone
mou mayowanai yeah...
I have no more doubts, yeah...
me no mae no genjitsu ni
to the truth before my eyes
he kon de shimau koto hoshi no kazu
to the things I give in to, the number of stars
yuugure no aka wo mita
I saw the redness of evening
boku ni hitsuyou na kawaranai yuuki
the unchanging courage that I need
boku wa boku de kimi wa kimi no
me and mine, you and yours
yuzurenai jounetsu
unyielding passion
me wo sorasazu ni tatakai tsuzukeru koto
don't turn your eyes away, continue to fight
We've gotta take the stars
sorezore no nido to nai toki wo kizamou
try to carve the moments that won't come again
shinjitsu wa Rhythm Nation
truth is Rhythm Nation
toki no nagare ni makenaide arukou
don't lose to the flow of time, walk...
You don't have to worry about tomorrow
This is a terrible injury.
Brago, rescue him now.
Don't be meddlesome.
What did you say?
Is there no such thing as kindness to you?
Throw away your optimism.
Be heartless.
Don't think you can change
a person by force alone!
Next time on Konjiki no Gash Bell:
Rumbling Snowfield!
A Regal Presence.
All those who fight me
will just understand
the foolishness of
making me their enemy.
Rumbling Snowfield!
A Regal Presence