ashita he tsuzuku sakamichi no tochuu de
On the uphill road that leads to tomorrow
surechigau otona tachi wa tsubuyaku no sa
We pass by adults who tell us this
"ai toka yume toka risou mo wakaru kedo
"I can understand ideals such as love and dreams
me no mae no genjitsu wa sonna ni amaku nai" tte
but the real world isn't as easy as you think"
tsumazuki nagara mo korogari nagara mo
Even though we keep tripping and falling
kasabuta darake no jyounetsu wo wasuretaku nai
We have to remember these pains of growing up
otona ni narenai bokura no
For all of us who can't force ourselves to do so yet
tsuyogari wo hitotsu kiite kure
Listen to this one thing I have to say
nige mo kakure mo shinai kara
I won't run or cower away
waraitai yatsu dake warae
So whoever wants to laugh at me, go ahead
semete tayori nai bokura no
Since we can't be relied upon yet
jiyuu no me wo tsumitoranai de
Don't take away our seed of freedom
mizu wo ageru sono yakume wo
The task of nurturing this plant
hataseba iindarou?
That's all we have to do, right?
Kiyomaro. Good morning.
It's c...cold.
I'm sorry. I'll close it.
What?
No wonder it's cold.
It snowed.
Gash.
Normally when it snows...
Kiyomaro. It's snow!
Snow has fallen.
Let's make a snowman together.
That's what you normally do...
Are you still upset about losing to Bali?
That's not it.
Indeed, Bali was strong.
Like him,
there are other demons
as strong as Brago.
Come to think of it,
I wonder what Brago and
Sherry are up to now?
Snowfield Rumble!! A Regal Presence
My Lady!
It's very dangerous to go that fast!
The monsters are nearby.
It's extremely dangerous
for you, so stay put.
I cannot do that.
Jee!
I... I am alright.
Leave him. Let's go.
Well, Brago?
The demon's scent is weak.
They already left.
We lost them again?
It's common these days, for them
to escape in the nick of time...
I was expecting a worthy challenger,
but they cowered
and ran away.
But... they made the right choice.
Those who fight me,
only realize their weakness.
Brago, what is it?
It's not a demon, but I sense danger.
How big...
Don't move.
At this rate, they'll be killed.
Jeff... Grab the gun!
Quickly, get revenge.
Reisu!
Grandpa!
Grandpa! Are you alright?!
The wounds are terrible.
We have to call for help.
Brago, give me a hand.
Jee. How are his wounds?
For now, his bleeding has stopped,
but he should see a doctor.
No, I am fine now.
There's a reason I
cannot leave this place.
But...
Don't overdo it.
On another note,
you said you wanted to get revenge?
Last year my daughter and her
husband, this boy's parents,
were bitten to death by that bear.
That's terrible.
Then why didn't you pick
up the gun and shoot it?
Coward.
Brago! Stop that.
How dare you say that to a child!
I hate cowards.
What are you saying?
Don't you have any sympathy?
Wait! Where are you going?
I'm going out for some exercise.
If I stay here with you,
my muscles will get stiff.
Go back to the hotel and get some rest.
What do you mean?
When did I say I needed to rest?
Don't say it as if I'm holding you back.
What's with his attitude?
For once he should
experience being powerless.
That's not it,
he's concerned about your health.
Oh, really?
Concerned about me...
he didn't seem so!
My Lady, you don't see that
Brago-sama has changed quite a bit.
At first he was dangerous and violent,
but now I see that he
has become dignified.
Brago?
Yes.
Strict and yet kind,
the presence of a king.
Jee.
You're flattering him.
That's not so.
As you say,
he seems to have lost
his destructive nature.
Out of my way, old man!
Don't interfere!
I will not.
I will not allow you to hurt
Lady Sherry any further!
You dare say that, old man?
I'll finish you right this minute!
I'm alright, Jee.
Please stand back.
But, my Lady.
Listen to me, Brago.
I was saying that we
should go somewhere else.
If we practice the spells here,
we will involve people
unnecessarily. Therefore-
Stop being a fool.
If they're unnecessary
then they don't matter.
Listen.
As irritating as this sounds,
I have to team up with a human
weakling like yourself.
Even if the demon is strong,
a weak human will cause him to lose!
Throw away any
unnecessary thoughts!
Be ruthless and bring out everything.
Ignite your anger and hatred.
Then bring forth the
power from the book!
If you don't... I'll tear him to pieces!
Then...
you shall never become a king.
I am your one and only bookkeeper.
Isn't that right?
That's why you're trying to subdue me.
If I die you can no
longer use your power.
You are just like her,
the one who manipulated
Koko's emotions, Zophise!
You only think of yourself.
Everyone else is beneath you.
Rather than obeying someone like that...
I'll slit my own throat!
My... Lady.
To you demons, I have
nothing but hatred.
Now, Brago.
If you want to become the King,
then obey me.
Or,
would you rather not become king
because of your selfishness?
Don't ever think that you can manipulate
the hearts of human beings!
Don't underestimate
humans that much!
You do not have the right
to become the king!
You think I'd steal your dinner?
In any case...
help me get some exercise.
Thank you. I'm quite warm now.
We'll have to head back
to the hotel before dark.
Please excuse us.
I'm in your debt.
Please be careful.
Jeff, I'm sorry about Brago.
He said mean things to you.
Brago.
You defeated it for Jeff.
Don't get me wrong.
I came across it in the forest
so I took it out.
Brago-sama has changed quite a bit.
Strict and yet kind,
the presence of a king.
Isn't it good? You have
avenged your parents.
Boy. Become stronger,
and never show your tears.
Crying will not get you anywhere.
Mind your own business.
Who asked you to do it?
I was going to get revenge
with my own hands!
Jeff.
I'm terribly sorry.
Deep inside he's relieved.
Not being honest about it,
sounds like someone we know.
I'm heading back to the hotel.
For goodness sakes.
Lady Sherry, good morning.
Good morning.
For once I was able to get
a good night's sleep.
That's good.
Where is Brago?
Brago-sama has already awoken
and said he'll go out
for some exercise,
before we start off today.
He's so self-centered.
Please stop.
Whatever you say, we shall
not leave this place.
Shut up!
If you're like that, we'll just bulldoze
you along with the cottage.
Bro, there's someone coming.
Who the hell are you?
Brago-sama.
These are conning real-estate agents.
Boy. Become stronger.
And never show your tears.
Crying will not get you anywhere.
Pray to become stronger,
and find the man's way.
This place belongs to me and
my grandfather. Go away!
You sound so manly, boy.
What if I say no?
I will... become stronger.
A man must not show tears!
This kid's a nuisance. Hey, here.
I won't lose!
A new spell?
What does this mean?
Could something be
happening to Brago?
I won't lose!
I won't lose.
Jeff...
No more, please!
Die!
What's with you?
You dare interfere?!
Get him!
Bulldoze them down!
Is it really alright?
You should run. There's no
point in getting involved.
You were saying "don't interfere"
and "bulldoze them".
Were you saying that to me?
No.
This guy... what an
overwhelming presence he has.
In that case, get out of my sight!
Yes. Excuse us.
But, bro. We can't back down like this.
It's alright.
Just in case,
I planted dynamite in the mountain.
Get what you deserve, you bastard!
Stay calm.
Dioga Gurabidon!
How did you know that I'd be here?
A new spell appeared,
and so I thought
something was going on.
Brago-sama.
Thank you very much,
for saving us from them.
Brago, you... helped them?
Don't mistake me.
I just wanted to swat
some noisy flies.
Big brother. I didn't run.
I will become a strong man.
Yeah.
You'll become much stronger.
Hmm, I see.
What?
You can smile.
It's the first time I saw it.
I'm not smiling.
Brago.
Brago-sama has changed quite a bit.
Strict and yet kind,
the presence of a king.
Let's go.
Brago,
if you like, we can stay for another day.
Be quiet. The demons
will elude us again.
Wait.
You're so self-centered.
Listen to me for a...
Oh, see you, Jeff.
Thank you!
Good bye!
Take care!
Wow. They've made something huge.
Takamine-kun.
Suzume, Umagon and I made this.
Isn't it great?
You didn't get my
permission to build this!
Stars atarashii mirai e to...
Stars, to the new tomorrow...
akiramenai hitori janai
don't give up, you are not alone
mou mayowanai yeah...
I have no more doubts, yeah...
me no mae no genjitsu ni
to the truth before my eyes
he kon de shimau koto hoshi no kazu
to the things I give in to, the number of stars
yuugure no aka wo mita
I saw the redness of evening
boku ni hitsuyou na kawaranai yuuki
the unchanging courage that I need
boku wa boku de kimi wa kimi no
me and mine, you and yours
yuzurenai jounetsu
unyielding passion
me wo sorasazu ni tatakai tsuzukeru koto
don't turn your eyes away, continue to fight
We've gotta take the stars
sorezore no nido to nai toki wo kizamou
try to carve the moments that won't come again
shinjitsu wa Rhythm Nation
truth is Rhythm Nation
toki no nagare ni makenaide arukou
don't lose to the flow of time, walk...
You don't have to worry about tomorrow
Kiyomaro, what is this exactly?
The words on this look
similar to our book.
Right.
I've seen this tablet before.
Right! Using our open minded thinking
we'll experiment on this tablet.
Right. I'm going to train with Tio.
Next time on Konjiki no Gash Bell:
A Wicked Thief!
The Mystery of the Tablet.
What I must do to make Gash the king?
The key is in this tablet!
A Wicked Thief!
The Mystery of the Tablet