ashita he tsuzuku sakamichi no tochuu de
On the uphill road that leads to tomorrow
surechigau otona tachi wa tsubuyaku no sa
We pass by adults who tell us this
"ai toka yume toka risou mo wakaru kedo
"I can understand ideals such as love and dreams
me no mae no genjitsu wa sonna ni amaku nai" tte
but the real world isn't as easy as you think"
tsumazuki nagara mo korogari nagara mo
Even though we keep tripping and falling
kasabuta darake no jyounetsu wo wasuretaku nai
We have to remember these pains of growing up
otona ni narenai bokura no
For all of us who can't force ourselves to do so yet
tsuyogari wo hitotsu kiite kure
Listen to this one thing I have to say
nige mo kakure mo shinai kara
I won't run or cower away
waraitai yatsu dake warae
So whoever wants to laugh at me, go ahead
semete tayori nai bokura no
Since we can't be relied upon yet
jiyuu no me wo tsumitoranai de
Don't take away our seed of freedom
mizu wo ageru sono yakume wo
The task of nurturing this plant
hataseba iindarou?
That's all we have to do, right?
Zonisu!
Rashirudo!
Heh. You're fighting seriously.
I've already prepared myself.
Oh? This boy...
For having to battle
strong guys like you!
Come!
Zakeruga!
Garuzonisu!
You're going to be a kind ruler.
In that case, there's
only one thing to do!
Yep. To defeat those guys!
I can't afford to lose!
You're determined to come at us again?
How interesting.
Endless Fight to the Death
Gash vs Bali
Let's end it with one strike!
Yeah!
Zakeru!
Heh. So they continue to struggle.
Shut up!
This is their final struggle.
It was the human who
received my blow after all.
I see.
So this human is not
intimidated by Bali's punch.
Heh. Looks like they still
think they can win.
Even after receiving your blow.
Gustav!
This time I'm serious.
I will seriously beat them to a pulp.
This guy... he still has so much power?
Let's give them our best!
Yeah!
Zakeruga!
What?
Zakeruga... he blocked it with his fist!
Gustav!
Alright!
Garuzonisu!
They're flying up here!
Gash! This way!
They're escaping to the right.
They've come after us!
Bit early to be falling down.
Who's down?
Are you able to withstand my attacks?
Gotcha!
Heh. Impertinent!
Gash, above you! Shoot up!
Go!
Zakeruga!
What? Dodged, at that range?
Idiot! As if such a move
could hit me when I'm ready!
Zonisu!
Their attack missed!
Kiyomaro, counterattack!
What's going on?
The floor crumbled.
A chance to attack...
...is done like this!
Gigano Zonisu!
This is bad.
At this rate, we're dead.
An escape...
Straight ahead is good enough.
An escape.
Zakeruga!
Please... let this...
Let this... anything but a direct hit...
Flag says "Tsuchinoko" which is a mythical animal.
Where is the spot Gash was at?
Hmm... I think... there was a chimney
somewhere around there...
It's not there.
That's strange... I'm
sure it was around there.
Hm? Oh, this is! A track
left by a tsuchinoko!
Oh? Really?
And it's still fresh!
Let's go!
Hey, you little... I'm going first!
Looks like it's over.
I guess he didn't get
what he was looking for.
Why? Why am I so annoyed?
With each enemy I defeat, I
come closer to being king.
That should be certain.
But there is something missing.
Even though I defeat
them, I am unsatisfied.
Instead, my irritation grows.
Gigano Zonisu!
I thought if I fought these guys,
my irritation would be relieved.
But these guys were the
same as all the others?
Oh? They're still alive?
I-I'm going to win.
I cannot lose here.
If I lose, I cannot become a kind ruler!
Yes, that wish... I will
definitely make it come true!
End it with the next shot.
Yeah!
Baou Zakeruga!
They are still able to...
Gustav.
Zorushirudo!
Kiyomaro!
How's that, demon? Even you...
Baou Zakeruga had no effect?
Not yet... My irritation is not yet relieved.
Why? Baou Zakeruga is our
most powerful attack.
Additionally, he took a direct hit.
Yet... how is he standing?
Worthless. Is that the limit, for you?
Damn it...
After using Baou Zakeruga,
my body won't move.
I can't use any more spells.
Not even a single Zakeru.
Kiyomaro. You've got to hold on.
As I expected. Looks like that's the end.
They didn't give me
what I wanted either.
It seems that we have
no more business here.
Gustav!
Zonisu!
This guy!
Actually blocked...
This time I'm striking first!
Damn it. Such an insolent move!
Huh? Why...
Those eyes of Gash...
D-Damn you!
He's gone?
Kiyomaro.
Kiyomaro, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Over there. In that shadow...
From here, I'll fight on my own.
You can stay here and rest.
I won't let them touch you.
I'm sorry. When my strength
returns, I'll back you up.
No need to hurry.
As you said, we can take
this a step at a time.
I'm going to move towards becoming
a kind ruler one step at a time.
Koruru.
Gash.
Thank you, everyone.
If only we had a kind ruler,
maybe we wouldn't need to
fight such a terrible battle.
A kind ruler?
You're right, Koruru.
I've decided.
I will survive and win
this battle. And then...
I will become a kind ruler.
Please do that, Gash.
Yeah. I won't give up.
Afterward, I'll do what I can.
Hmph. They ran away.
No. I wonder about that.
Up for this again?
This guy, he's after my...
You're going to give me that book.
Bastard!
You're too persistent!
You really want me to finish you off?
What?
That's?
The human!
That guy... He's trying to
collapse the ceiling on top of us.
Damn it... Stupid thing...
You're not going to move anymore?
Nevermind. I still have an option.
I'm still able to fight them.
Damn you. Hand over the
book already! Do as I say!
Who...
Darn, I can't move.
Kiyomaro.
Damn it!
I will not let you pass!
Out of the way!
I... cannot... let you through.
Still talking!
Gash...
I'm sorry... my body refuses to move.
Kiyomaro must rest.
I am still able to keep trying.
Gash... thank you.
You are so persistent!
Gash...
Give up and die already!
Finishing blow!
Gash!
Again...
My hand stopped again.
Why? Why am I frightened of his eyes?
Frightened by this worn out little kid,
who can't use any more spells?
Why?
You said your name was Gash.
May I ask one thing?
What kind of ruler are
you striving to become?
A kind ruler!
Hmph. That is the kind of path it is.
The reason you let an
unimportant thing escape earlier...
was to hold straight to your ambition?
Thanks to that, you put yourself
at a disadvantage.
Still, you wish to be a kind ruler?
Despite that...
that is the only type of king I could be.
This fight ends here.
What?
Gustav!
Bali, what kind of ruler
do you wish to be?
You just defeat the
enemies in front of you.
You, who only believes in
the ideal of a hooligan...
...cannot defeat his
eyes of true aspiration.
Don't be ridiculous!
A kind ruler?
You expect me to admit
defeat to this little brat?
Then Bali... I will ask you once again.
What kind of ruler will you be?
A strong one.
No matter who my opponent is, I will
silence him with a single blow.
A strong ruler!
One who will lose to no one,
the strongest king!
As I expected from you.
Fine. That is a notch higher
than a mere hooligan.
Gash. And Kiyomaro, wasn't it?
I will let you go this time.
Your "kind ruler" or my strength...
Which one is more suited to be the new
king will be revealed eventually.
That book... I will leave it intact for now.
Gustav.
To be the strong ruler,
what must I do now?
It's no good fighting like before,
without a thought, correct?
Hmph. You must contemplate
a lot of things.
Oh, I will contemplate them.
This has begun to get interesting.
Looks like Bali got what he wanted.
Kiyomaro and Gash.
I give you my gratitude...
for giving Bali an opportunity to change.
But do not forget, I could have
burned your book at any time.
You two must grow even more.
Let us meet again. I shall look
forward to our next encounter.
And I'll help with the rest...
I'll teach you...
I'll do something about it.
Yes.
What did I mean,
"I'll do something about it"?
We lost...
We lost.
Stars atarashii mirai e to...
Stars, to the new tomorrow...
akiramenai hitori janai
don't give up, you are not alone
mou mayowanai yeah...
I have no more doubts, yeah...
me no mae no genjitsu ni
to the truth before my eyes
he kon de shimau koto hoshi no kazu
to the things I give in to, the number of stars
yuugure no aka wo mita
I saw the redness of evening
boku ni hitsuyou na kawaranai yuuki
the unchanging courage that I need
boku wa boku de kimi wa kimi no
me and mine, you and yours
yuzurenai jounetsu
unyielding passion
me wo sorasazu ni tatakai tsuzukeru koto
don't turn your eyes away, continue to fight
We've gotta take the stars
sorezore no nido to nai toki wo kizamou
try to carve the moments that won't come again
shinjitsu wa Rhythm Nation
truth is Rhythm Nation
toki no nagare ni makenaide arukou
don't lose to the flow of time, walk...
You don't have to worry about tomorrow
I wonder what kind of person
Umagon's Book Keeper is?
Where are you going?
Oh! At last we've found
the Book Keeper!
Next time on Konjiki no Gash Bell:
Umagon! Critical danger!
We're going to work together
and deliver the presents.
Meru Meru Mee!
Umagon Critical Danger?!